

Juan Pablo Llorente

Full Stack Web Developer

CONTACT

Buenos Aires, Argentina

M juanpablollorentej@amail.com

+54 11 3336-5620

in Juan-Pablo-Llorente

JuanPablo-Llorente

Portfolio

EDUCATION

Henry Bootcamp

Full Stack Web Developer 2021 - 2022

Edutin Academy

Some IT related courses 2021 - 2022

Raggio Technical School

Master Builder 2015 - 2020

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native. English: Intermediate.

INTERESTS









Read

PROFILE

I'm a 20 years old Full Stack Web Developer and Master Builder from Buenos Aires, Argentina. Mainly oriented to the Back End, though i like Front End too.

As a good lover of logic, performance and order, I always seek to perform in the user experience and write a clean code.

I'm passionate about the technological and computer world and I always find myself learning new things.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer

Henry

May 2022 - June 2022

An digital art e-commerce with a small social network system. Made with six more co-workers as final project.

Full Stack Web Developer

Henry

April 2022 - May 2022

A SPA (Single Page Application) of a video games encyclopedia.

DevOps

ABEM

March 2022 - April 2022

Assembly of mining platforms and do their maintenance.

AutoCAD Draftsman

MT Arquitectura

Sept. 2020 - August 2021

Drawing of municipal plans.

CERTIFICATES

Full Stack Web Developer - June 2022 →

Computer Security - May 2022 →

Mobile Phone Repair and Maintenance - May 2022 →

Fundamentals in Computer Science - May 2022 →

Introduction to C - July 2021 →

MAIN SKILLS

- JavaScript
- CSS
- Redux
- **Express**
- Sequelize

- HTML
- React
- Node
- PostgreSQL
- Git